bundlr.com 2013-08-05

# Bundlr - Privacy Policy

We at Bundlr ("we" or Bundlr) have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your personal information and informing you about how we handle it. This privacy policy only applies to transactions and activities in which you engage, and data gathered, on the bundlr.com, gobundlr.com websites (and sub-domains) but does not apply to any other Website or offline point of contact between bundlr.com, or any other company, and consumers. Please review this privacy policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time. This privacy policy was last revised on October 26, 2011. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time. 

Personal Information
     For some activities on Bundlr, such as creating, publishing and adding notes to bundles, you may be required to create an account. When registering for an account on the Website, we ask for certain personal information, including your name and email address. We may also ask for other personal information to assist us with enhancing the Website and improving the user experience. 
Automated Information
     We may also automatically collect non-personally identifiable information about your computer or mobile device when you access the Website. For example, when you visit Bundlr.com, we may collect information about your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, the type of browser software you are using, the operating system you are running, the site, if any, that referred you, the date and time of your visit, as well as the pages you visit on the Website. If you use a mobile device or application to access Bundlr’s services, we may also collect information about your mobile device, such as the type of device you use. 
Profile and Notes
     Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose in your profile or in your notes or bundles is public. Bundlr may choose to collect any such personal information. 
Accessing and Modifying Your Personal Information
     You can access your personal information by logging in and clicking on “Edit your Profile.” From there, you can change the email address associated with your account or delete your account. 
Legal Disclaimer
     While Bundlr generally makes every effort to preserve your privacy and does not sell, transfer or otherwise disseminate your personally identifiable information to outside parties, it reserves the right to do so under certain circumstances: 

  * **Third Parties**  
In limited circumstances, Bundlr may provide personal information to trusted third parties to provide support for the operation of the Website. Personal information will only be disclosed subject to an appropriate confidentiality and security agreement, and only to the extent necessary to perform these support functions. 
  * **Disclosures Required by Law**  
We may disclose your information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, or when doing so is reasonably necessary to: comply with a law, regulation or legal process; to respond to any claims; to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of any person; to address security or technical issues; or to protect against fraud, misuse or unauthorized use of the Website. 
  * **Business Transitions**  
In addition, your personal information may be disclosed as part of any merger, sale, acquisition, bankruptcy or transfer of company assets. 

Information Security
     While we use reasonable measures to safeguard personal information, Bundlr cannot absolutely guarantee the security of the personal information you supply to us, or the security of our servers and databases. Personal information may be stored on computers of third parties who have access to your personal information subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Bundlr does not control the security measures used by such third parties. By using the Website, you assume all risks associated with the potential loss of personal information. 
Third Party Links And Content
     Bundlr does not control the privacy policies of its partners or other social media sites to which it provides links or access, and the information collection and dissemination policies of such companies are not governed by Bundlr’s Privacy Policy. As a result, if you decide to make use of any of these third-party sites or services, you should review their privacy policies. 

Questions about this Privacy Policy should be sent to [support@bundlr.com](mailto:support@bundlr.com).
